yo yo periscope what up I said we were
back we almost didn't come back cuz our
trunk is open and we have a large
television hanging out the back but is
this amount of extra stuff we have oh
you can see Oh oh my god oh god I'm
trusting open pilot to drive the
televisions home I'm gonna make a change
here nice and smooth
[Music]
we have a big TV in the truck that's
right something pulled over we did say
we'd come back we're kind of like I
don't really want to come back but you
know for the live streaming people we
are honest live streamers oh and there's
doing any good no I don't think so I
think that boy that the TV's gonna stay
with us it's the more it's gonna lose us
and then we have watching me yeah you
know what I mean like maybe we were too
crazy with two TVs
oh we were the guys like two TVs yeah
begin Amino this is reflective of how we
actually use open pilot it's a lot like
autopilot just well um you know help you
out with a lot of scenarios
assistant system - is press conference
well it's a press conference so we're
inviting the press by for appointments
on Wednesday and Thursday
could you see live no you can't it's
actually gonna be an embargo until
Friday at 6 p.m. but we're gonna be back
live Friday at noon I'm gonna demo the
new product fabulous that'll be so much
more exciting
it's good
we got to be over there wouldn't be nice
of open file help us out with that
Comstock
coming soon zero points for comments it
well people came back quick I know
people were waiting for it um so maybe
we'll continue down Route one and we'll
take slope huh okay yeah yeah just cuz I
don't really want to get to that Lane
yeah this thing might kind of work on
Route one let's see what we can do so I
think this next turn is gonna be above
the torque planet now that's another
great advantage of mapping we're gonna
know exactly which turns are above the
torque limit we're already putting our
dis engagements on a map
spoiler alert maybe that's one of the
things we'll put on the big TV oh we got
tickles we've got a table TVs
TCL I can't even show you because we
don't even have the good size but
[Music]
truly did it again are we gonna get
breakout we're gonna get breaker breaker
no gap created self-driving cars because
we failed with flying cars here uber is
working on flying cars next we're
chopper you know they do real news
super chopper is pretty fun old at North
Cal recently itself of a pilot on his
father's car
exciting exciting wait really fifteen
year olds drive you are aware that if
you're using open pilot you still need a
driver's license right nor account maybe
they got like farms out there really
farming kids driving the father's car
yeah but
we'll take the barking fruit again yeah
I think use it responsibility is that
shooting laser at the top it's not have
any lasers
you see this turn here yeah so this is
what open pilot has gotten so much
better at recently this one is a little
bit alright wants to go that way let's
go
one-lane yeah so notice that I'm right
now it's driving with one lane marker
and again we're gonna get a
disengagement here for the red light
okay we're gonna look into all that it
will be fixed well I'll tweet that
shouldn't be it's not in release it's
only in our stuff you can't give the
best - you know because we test and then
we make what we release next even better
if you would think that we would be
driving with the best of the best
oh no everybody when you worked at
Facebook internally you use internal
buggy Facebook yeah sounds awful you use
the beta of your product every company
does that I will sign on to a fatalist
oh that was something sliding yep chunk
is open trunk is open is the TV on the
ground
let's put twit this blinker on just we
can see the outside of this oh wow that
was that was a responsive
um so yeah I mean open pilot is is just
learning how to start to drive these
sort of streets it doesn't okay job
yeah I mean this is this is stunning
there's no like trick here that you can
have already in release open
one of our top drivers was driving at 14
yeah yeah yeah I mean yeah some of the
states some of the states really Alaska
does our last damn sure 17 No
[Music]
turning here oh my god did you forget we
have TV I forgot we had beauties I think
we're good I think the TV has made it
alright well just we'll get out I'll
show the people the TVs any last
questions questions I'll show you the
TVs Thank You Honda Honda what was
terrifying that turn yeah show him a
tickle tickle
and any Best Buy near you
oh no we bought them at Target no no now
listen listen that's pie's cool we went
to Best Buy every possible target and
then we price match with Best Buy yeah
we did they would only price match one
TV all right thanks later people